I've heard that a pack of wolves disperse
as soon as you strike their leader.
Crap! I feel lightheaded.
So hot!
Yow! Yikes!
What did he do?
Maybe he touched a weird spot?
Hey! The girl's getting away!
Get her!
Look out!
The fence is falling down!
Let's get outta here quick!
We're gonna be crushed!
Dunno what's going on,
but now's my chance!
Whoa.
What a great view.
Good thing this happened
to be a run-down hot springs.
Talk about lucky.
Yep, I sure am.
Turbo Granny? What are you doing here?
Don't underestimate me.
It clicked when Seiko
mentioned the boy's address.
That it was hot springs territory.
That's why I stealthily
snuck into your backpack.
Why can't you just ask to come?
More like, what am I gonna do
about this building?
Forget it, it was already run-down.
It's not like I did anything.
Damn it! What the heck?
Ow.
Who the hell did all this?
Are you the ones responsible?
Hey! These guys are from the Kito family!
You guys are still up to no good?
Crap! Those are Chamber of Commerce guys!
Stop!
Scumbags! I hope you're locked up forever!
Whew, that was a good bath.
You saved me. Thanks.
Who would ever save you?
The powers within this vessel
just came out on their own.
I guess so.
Anyway, did you see Jiji's house?
What do you think, Turbo Granny?
I couldn't see anything at all.
That place is no good.
That house has soaked up
too much human blood.
Wicked! What is this?
What should we do, Okarun?
I'm not sure, either.
For now, let's wait
until Miss Ayase comes back.
It's dangerous
to haphazardly jump in there.
Miss Ayase is back.
Nice timing!
Momo! I found something...
You know that stupid family on the corner?
They never say hello!
Really. That makes me sick.
This is our territory after all.
People who don't know about manners
need to be taught a lesson.
Jin, don't just stand there.
Sit down and have some snacks.
Thanks!
That's right, you better stay friendly.
You don't have to pay rent
because I'm so thoughtful.
Thanks!
Kids have such a hard time
when their parents are so weak.
If it weren't for us, you'd be out
on the street with nowhere to go.
That's right. You should be grateful.
Mr. Jiji, what's the meaning of this?
This is a rental house.
While my parents are hospitalized,
I don't have to pay rent.
These folks are the Kitos, the landlords.
Thanks to them, I can stay in this house.
Then, we really did
a bad thing to that wall.
If they ask, say you don't know.
Hey, Jin.
You disappeared without telling us.
My friend said he wanted to come visit,
so I went to go pick him up!
I can at least do that, right?
Not that I think you would,
but you didn't try to bring in another
spirit medium or something, did you?
Huh? Gimme a break already!
We don't have any ghosts
around here, you dimwit!
Are you trying to ruin
our property's good reputation?
Don't go around lying
to people about ghosts!
Oh, no.
Does he look like a spirit medium to you?
I was simply fooled by those other people!
I have a hunter's license, you know?
Unfortunate accidents happen
pretty often in the mountains.
For instance, if I was hunting a boar,
and a person just happened
to jump in front of me.
Oh, come on, now.
Even if you have a license,
pointing a gun at people
will get you in trouble with the police.
Hello there!
Man, that was a pain.
The Chamber of Commerce guys found us.
If Officer Tsuru didn't help us out,
we'd have been in trouble.
That place was way too run-down.
We have to find our next spot.
It's troublesome for me
if you're too reckless.
It's hard dealing with the aftermath.
What did you guys do this time?
That's a secret from you, Mom.
If anyone in the Kito family
gets arrested, it's your fault, Tsuru.
Yo, Jin! Where have you been?
Well, I was out with my friend.
Don't you dare lie, okay?
I hate liars more than anything else.
Sure.
Who's this guy?
Oh, he's my best friend,
and he wanted to come visit.
So what's Jin's favorite soccer team?
You'd know if you were
his best friend, right?
Um, he's...
Jin, you stay quiet.
It's not like you guys just met, is it?
If you weren't actually his best friend,
I'd have to ask why
Jin brought you to this house.
Z...
Zaint-Germain.
Well, well!
You do know.
He's Jin's best friend.
Okarun! Nice one!
Hey, Jin!
There was one more. A girl.
When's she coming back?
Let's see, a girl. I wonder who that is?
Come on, Jin. Are you telling the truth?
Huh? Well, yes.
You did yourself in just now.
You lied to us.
This must be the shrine
for the tsuchinoko, right?
But more like, what's up with that guy?
Do you need anything?
Oh, um...
Is this the tsuchinoko shrine?
Oh, yes.
Apologies for the awkward sight.
I'm trying to become a BooTuber.
Please, come on in.
Are you sure it's okay to show me?
Isn't that valuable?
Not at all.
I can't make any money
off of something like this.
Man, I wanna be a BooTuber.
Wow, I can't wait!
I should come back here again with Okarun!
A tsuchinoko?
Doesn't look like it.
I agree with you.
GREAT SERPENT LORD
According to documents
remaining in this shrine,
"Dragon rising to heaven
will cast a rainbow,
and the wrath of the mountain
will engulf the village."
This region worshipped a giant snake.
It was believed that
when the giant snake living in the volcano
gets hungry, the volcano erupts.
Back then, the people offered
one child from the village as a sacrifice
to satiate the giant snake's hunger.
By doing so for the past 200 years,
it has kept the volcano from erupting,
and was even granted
the blessing of hot springs.
The thing that looks like
an umbilical cord is supposedly
from when the giant snake molted.
Nowadays, by enshrining
that giant snake skin,
it's preventing the volcano from erupting.
Then, what about the tsuchinoko?
My father said
there would be more tourists
if we called it a tsuchinoko.
Son of a...
But thanks to that,
people like you do come visit.
This legend of the giant snake
is a human sin.
People who are robbed
of logical thinking due to fear
can believe in and even execute
human sacrifices.
So we don't repeat such sins,
I take the time
and tell visitors of this tale.
Although I really want to become
a headstand BooTuber.
Wait, why don't you tell
that story on BooTube?
There was no tsuchinoko.
Okarun is going to be really disappointed.
But he might like that old,
local folktale story.
Okay, then.
I wonder if the two boys
are deepening their friendship.
I'm home. Did the ghosts show up?
Our offerings are finally all here.
Now let's start our festival.
Ouch.
Boobies!
Crap. I'm getting dizzy.
There, there.
Good girl. Don't be scared.
God damn turd!
Ow.
Just when I was sleeping soundly...
Who the hell was squishing me like that?
Turbo Granny! Thanks!
And it'd help a ton
if you could lend me a hand.
I ain't gonna help ya.
So, who are these guys?
That's what I wanna know!
Calm down, young lady.
Stay away from me!
Get outta this house right now!
Hurry up!
That hurt.
Is she for real?
Jennifer!
Lopez!
Anaconda!
Mom is the strongest
old woman in the Kito family!
Who exactly is that girl?
It seemed like she was using
some sort of strange power.
What exactly is that old hag?
She's just a powerful old hag.
Like they actually exist.
You got one in your own house.
True.
Mom, look at that!
Things are floating,
and there's a talking cat!
More like, what's with this room?
It's seriously gross!
Who the hell is this?
She doesn't seem to be a spirit medium.
If you're getting
in the way of the festival,
then that means you're here
to destroy this village.
The Kito family has protected
this land for generations.
We won't let you have your way.
Huh?
You barged into someone's house,
thrashed it all up,
and that's what you say?
Get out of here!
Come on now.
Who do you think is responsible
for letting you bathe
in the hot springs in peace?
It's because we've been giving offerings
to the Great Serpent Lord
for the past 200 years!
Thanks to that, the volcano
is held back from erupting,
and we're given the blessing of
the Great Serpent Lord
through the hot springs.
If we, the Kito family,
didn't manage this land,
this village would be buried
in magma by now.
Hold on a second! Did you say
you were offering sacrifices?
Yeah. You deaf?
This place is
where the original altar was.
This is where human sacrifices were made.
Its appearance changed with the times,
but this house is still that altar.
And we of the Kito family
invite sacrifices into this house,
and offer them to the Great Serpent Lord.
No way.
So that's why Jiji's parents...
We lucked out.
We have exactly three people.
We were almost short on offerings.
The Great Serpent Lord
is quite hungry right now.
What the hell is this?
Crap!
The floor turned into sand!
Wanna go at it, huh?
I have to get out of here!
Think you can take me?!
I won't let you cross this threshold.
You'll be swallowed up by that quicksand
and become
the Great Serpent Lord's offering!
This is seriously bad!
Turbo Granny, do something!
We've stepped into the quicksand!
Into the Great Serpent Lord's realm!
Miss Ayase, over here!
Before it's too late!
Momo! Use your psychic powers!
Both of you, nice one! You're a lifesaver!
Okarun, are you okay?
Somehow...
Wait, are you serious?
How the hell are we gonna get back?
What the hell are all these houses?
Why are there so many underground?
Momo! Okarun! Help me!
Jiji! Where are you?
Over here!
Jiji!
I'm gonna fall!
I'll help you right now!
Great Serpent Lord!
How blessed we are by your arrival!
We, the Kito family,
are your faithful emissaries!
Get the pose right or it'll eat you!
That's the Great Serpent Lord!
I've never seen it before.
On this occasion,
we present those three as sacrifices.
Please do not mistake them
for members of the Kito Family!
Great Serpent Lord?
You mean the one in this region's legend?
Crap! It wasn't just a myth?
That's a Kuragari.
What the hell is a Kuragari?
You know what that is?
It's a Mongolian Death Worm!
It's a giant man-eating earthworm UMA
said to live in the Gobi Desert!
But the stories about it
say it's about 1.5 to two meters long.
I've never heard
of a Death Worm this huge!
Then for the past 200 years,
those guys have been offering
sacrifices to an earthworm UMA?
Now, Great Serpent Lord!
Please feast on those three there!
Hey! Gimme a break, damn hag!
That's not a god you're worshipping!
That's just a man-eating earthworm!
Be appeased...
It ate them!
What are we gonna do about this?
There's no way we can
defeat something like this!
This is definitely bad.
Let's hide inside a house for now!
Yeah, we can't stay outside.
Both of you, hurry!
That thing will spot you!
What's wrong? Are both of you okay?
Everyone, let's go!
Yeah!
The savage legend of the Great Serpent!
Naki Kito! Work at hand never fails!
That which is born from evil conventions...
Its name is...
Next episode, "The Evil Eye"!